{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "Answer: take", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (base form).", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["take", "to", "of", "search"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: lion", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["captured", "him", "lion", "later"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["they", "a", "that", "zoo"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["few", "hunters", "to", "and"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: later", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["later", "and", "few", "hunters"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["him", "of", "in", "wagon"]}, {"explanation": "tied is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and _____________ him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["went", "was", "tied", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "by is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled _____________ the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["by", "after", "that", "of"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["go", "that", "his", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: idea", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["tickled", "the", "idea", "The"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: in", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["to", "take", "in", "they"]}, {"explanation": "mouse is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the _____________ being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["search", "mouse", "idea", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "search is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in _____________ of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["wagon", "search", "zoo", "tree"]}, {"explanation": "tree is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["tree", "search", "mouse", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: and", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["able", "and", "the", "mouse"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After _____________ they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["that", "in", "by", "of"]}, {"explanation": "was is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion _____________ so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["tied", "was", "went", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "After is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["of", "after", "After", "by"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: being", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (present participle).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["and", "mouse", "being", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["him", "tied", "later", "the"]}, {"explanation": "wagon is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a _____________ , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["search", "idea", "wagon", "mouse"]}, {"explanation": "help is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to _____________ him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["help", "take", "go", "let"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: able", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["able", "the", "so", "him"]}], "success": 1}